[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray", "Mr. Jackson"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Who caused the death of Michael Jackson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Dr. Murray's repeated incompetent and unskilled acts that led to Mr. Jackson's death.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Because you can argue it's either way, can't you, on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Who had the better day, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, you know, it's tough to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackson", "Murray"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is that really the crux of this court case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes, the defense is a little bit multilayered in that they're saying that Jackson had a horrible insomnia problem and he used Propofol to get over it and Murray when he came on board understood this and used this as well with the anticipation of weaning him off of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "What was your reaction to those two things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "I saw that this morning, and when I heard the tape, I could not believe what I was hearing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "I mean, if that doesn't show you, don't you think that was enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes, I mean, what does it show you, though, given that it was taken -- the recording was made in May before he died, two months or so before he died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "DT", ",", "WRB", ",", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "What does that tell you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "That's what I was wondering, A, why, Michael would never let anyone tape him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Did you find it suspicious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I thought it was very suspicious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Jackson"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Did you see Conrad Murray at all that day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I saw him standing outside of the room where Mrs. Jackson and the family and the cousins were, and the children, just crying and not understanding what was going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What do you think the family believe really happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "To tell you the truth, I think that they have all been in such pain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "And I believe that he really trusted that this doctor would be there to be helpful and on call and -- I say that again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "No, listen, Kathy, I know this is a very difficult thing to discuss and I do appreciate you coming on today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "I'm curious, is it actually lawful for any doctor to administer Propofol in a private home in this manner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "You know, it's interesting, Piers, because the law's a little bit vague on this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "From a medical standpoint, as a doctor, do you find that suspicious or do you think that someone who has just seen Michael Jackson die in his care has just freaked out a bit and maybe just wasn't thinking straight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "No, I think it's suspicious.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Does any of that sound credible to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, you know, at first -- I mean I'll preface by saying the whole thing is so bizarre.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What was your initial assessment of the behavioral pattern today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, I think that it's going to be very important that the audience knows, Piers, that seven of these jurors actually have drug or alcohol abuse in their immediate families.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "How much does that come into play in a case like this, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "It's a tremendously important component for the prosecutors because prosecutors around the country are always worried that they have to step up to the plate and create situations such as \"CSI\" does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "How did he do today, do you think, in laying out his case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "David did an excellent job in his opening statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "What was your feeling as the day unraveled?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "You know, I had the same feeling as the counsel that just spoke earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Is that going to be a major problem for him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I absolutely think that he made up ground today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "How significant is this debate over his health before he died, do you think, going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I think it's very significant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Is that a credible position for them to take, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "It's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Is it fair to just label him as somebody who has been negligent and simply just allowed Michael Jackson to take far too many drugs and die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I don't think it's fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Is there a reasonable doubt as to that or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Gentlemen, thank you all very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Why is it so important to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "It's important to me because I think there's an injustice being done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What kind of things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "They didn't sequester the jury.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "So you watched him save your life, effectively?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "For people who don't know Conrad Murray, what is the misunderstanding about the kind of man he is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "The misunderstanding about Conrad is his compassion and his love for people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "And particularly, what were you thinking when you heard that Conrad was there at the time and had been the doctor that night in the house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I was at home.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What's your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "He's the most compassionate man that I've ever met.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Do you think he saved your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "How did Conrad find himself in this position?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I spoke with him before he went to work with Michael.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Is that a picture you could recognize?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Is it possible that he was negligent, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Let me share something with you and I'd like to elaborate on that a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "How do you plead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Your honor, I'm an innocent man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "As somebody that knows the man well and believes he saved your life, how do you feel about the way his reputation has been put through the mincer like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Basically, Piers, the reason I'm here is to let people know he is not the animal that they are portraying him to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "So when people say that he is greedy and was only working for Michael Jackson for money and fame and so on, what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "That's ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Money was not his motivating factor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "He has never -- or in the last five years, charged me for any office calls, any examinations, nothing, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "That's why he was broke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Is Conrad Murray the kind of man that in that situation, when he probably needed the money, and probably enjoyed the attachment to Michael Jackson -- could you have imagined him bowing to that kind of pressure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Ruby, if required, will you give evidence on his behalf in court?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Certainly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "In your case, Ruby, what did he do for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "OK, in my case, let me tell you, I was having problems with my heart and didn't even know it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ruby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "In your view, his quick thinking saved your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "No, his quick thinking and proactiveness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Could he have had his judgment impaired, do you think, by that dynamic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Anything's possible, but I doubt it very seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "What do you think is the right verdict here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Piers, if I knew all of the -- all of the fundamentals of this case, I might be able to answer that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Your belief, like all of you, is that there's no way he would have done anything to have deliberately imperiled Michael Jackson's life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Absolutely no doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "None of you believe that is possible, knowing Conrad Murray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Not somebody who works the way that he works with people, and comes to your house to make sure you are all right, and works for free.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}]